export const quizJSON = [
  {
    question: "What is the main ingredient in guacamole?",
    answer: "Avocado",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which Italian dish features thin sheets of pasta layered with cheese and meat sauce?",
    answer: "Lasagna",
  },
  {
    question: "What type of seafood is often used in traditional paella?",
    answer: "Shrimp",
  },
  {
    question: "In which country did the sandwich originate?",
    answer: "England",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which fruit is known as the 'king of fruits' and has a distinctive smell?",
    answer: "Durian",
  },
  {
    question: "Which type of cheese is often used in traditional Greek salads?",
    answer: "Feta",
  },
  {
    question: "In which country did the dish known as 'sushi' originate?",
    answer: "Japan",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the Korean dish made with fermented vegetables, typically cabbage or radishes?",
    answer: "Kimchi",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the traditional Middle Eastern dip made from mashed chickpeas, tahini, lemon juice, and garlic?",
    answer: "Hummus",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the Mexican dish that consists of a rolled tortilla filled with meat, beans, and cheese?",
    answer: "Burrito",
  },
];
